Guide to the Margaret Hodges Papers, 1911-2006 SC.1990.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Media, 1947-1988; VIII.
  - 35mm Slides, 4.
    - Elizabeth Nesbitt Room
      - Correspondence and Finding Aid (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Elizabeth Nesbitt Room Artifacts, 0 slides (Box 43, Folder 6-7)
      - The Elizabeth Nesbitt Room, Produced by Michael Estep, Includes Slide List and Label (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Public Libraries (donated by Frank B. Sessa)
      - Eastern United States (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Whitehall Township (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Springfield (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Carnegie Institute, Pgh.; Cheyenne, WY; Colorado Springs, CO; East Liberty, Pgh.; East Orange, NJ; Lawrenceville, Pgh.; Madison, WI; Mount Washington, Pgh.; Nashville, TN; Norfolk, VA; Wylie Avenue, Pgh. (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Carnegie Library (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Miami Public Library (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - University of Miami (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - East Liberty and Squirrel Hill (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Emmaus, Glenside, Levittown, Reading, Shaler, State College, and Willow Grove (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Beechview, Eastchester, and Larchmont (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Bay County, Buckhorn, Damariscotta, Damariscotta Mills, Hamlin (Paris, ME), Hollowell, Lithgo (Augusta, ME), Norway, Readfield, Wayne, and Winthrop (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Allapattah, Dixie Park, Edison Center, Fairlawn, GP?, LR?, New Lemon City, Old Lemon City, Shenandoah, WF? (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Loose Slides and Lists
      - Loose Slides, Including Fred Rogers (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - Lists Pertaining to Slides (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Oversize, 1969-2002; IX.
  Galleys, page proofs, and illustrations for Hodges' works. Note that this series does not include original illustrations, but rather scans and photocopies of originals.
  - Objects
    - Hope S. Dean Memorial Award figurine, 2002 (Box 45)
    - Matted Honorary Degree from Point Park College, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Galleys and Proofs, 1969-1999; 1.
    - Comus, Galley 1, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Comus, Galley 2, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Gulliver in Lilliput, Galley 1, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Gulliver in Lilliput, Galley 2, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Gulliver in Lilliput, Galley 3, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Hidden in Sand, Galley, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - The Hero of Bremen, Text Proof 1, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - The Hero of Bremen, Text Proof 2, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - The Hero of Bremen, Text Proof 3, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Hidden in the Sand, Uncorrected Proofs, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Joan of Arc, Uncorrected Proof, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Lady Queen Anne, Galley, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Storytelling, for the Encyclopedia of Library and Information Sciences, Galley (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - The True Tale of Johnny Appleseed, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Up The Chimney, Text Proof, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - The Little Humpbacked Horse, proof, Circa 1980 (Map-case 1, Drawer 7, Folder 1)
  - Illustrations, 1989-2002; 2.
    - The Arrow and the Lamp, 1989 (Map-case 1, Drawer 7, Folder 15)
    - Comus (Map-case 1, Drawer 7, Folder 16)
    - The Legend of St. Christopher, 2002 (Map-case 1, Drawer 7, Folder 17)
    - St. Patrick and the Peddler, 1993 (Map-case 1, Drawer 7, Folder 18)